<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Gopalakrishnan&#39;s Blog </title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Gopalakrishnan&#39;s Blog </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>gopalakrishnan.shanker@gmail.com (Gopalakrishnan Shanker Rajhan)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>gopalakrishnan.shanker@gmail.com (Gopalakrishnan Shanker Rajhan)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding the relationship between drugs and psyche</title>
      <link>/2018/10/12/drugs-and-psyche/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>gopalakrishnan.shanker@gmail.com (Gopalakrishnan Shanker Rajhan)</author>
      <guid>/2018/10/12/drugs-and-psyche/</guid>
      <description>This article is a slight edit from a group project paper I had done as a part of the coursework for STAT430 - Applied Machine Learning
IntroductionThe problem of drug abuse is a pressing concern. It has numerous factors associated with it that include environmental, social, psychological and economic. There has been plenty of coverage towards the social and economic factors. Here, we consider the psychological. Namely, the relationship between personality traits and proclivity to gravitate towards certain types of drugs to evaluate the risk of an individual being a drug consumer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Website - and My First Post!</title>
      <link>/2018/10/01/why-i-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>gopalakrishnan.shanker@gmail.com (Gopalakrishnan Shanker Rajhan)</author>
      <guid>/2018/10/01/why-i-blog/</guid>
      <description>This has been something I have wanted to start for a while. Pretty much everyone whose career path I have looked to learn from has suggested starting a blog to display your skills, whether that be about football (of the soccer variety) analysis or any other data science work.  A blog was supposed to be a public portfolio of my work, evidence of my capabilities for everyone to see. While that by itself was quite a nice reason to start a blog (I could network easier and maybe even gain employment), I was always putting it off until I saw another purpose put forward for having a blog - as a record of my personal progress and a collection of all the topics I delve into and try to understand.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>