<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Gopalakrishnan&#39;s Blog </title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Gopalakrishnan&#39;s Blog </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>gopalakrishnan.shanker@gmail.com (Gopalakrishnan Shanker Rajhan)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>gopalakrishnan.shanker@gmail.com (Gopalakrishnan Shanker Rajhan)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rite of Passage - Building an Expected Goals Model in R</title>
      <link>/2019/04/17/xg/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>gopalakrishnan.shanker@gmail.com (Gopalakrishnan Shanker Rajhan)</author>
      <guid>/2019/04/17/xg/</guid>
      <description>IntroductionSometimes, when I’m reading about an event that happened in the 2000s or reminiscing with friends about the past, one topic always stands out as something to be marveled at - the pace of technology. 12 years back, the first iPhone had just been released. It did not have an app store. Literally nobody had a ’smart’phone. Today, its presence is unavoidable in urban settings. I inevitably trip over how much the landscape of personal tech has changed since then.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Website - and My First Post!</title>
      <link>/2019/02/01/why-i-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>gopalakrishnan.shanker@gmail.com (Gopalakrishnan Shanker Rajhan)</author>
      <guid>/2019/02/01/why-i-blog/</guid>
      <description>This has been something I have wanted to start for a while. Pretty much everyone whose career path I have looked to learn from has suggested starting a blog to display your skills, whether that be about football (of the soccer variety) analysis or any other data science work. A blog can be a public portfolio of my work, evidence of my capabilities for everyone to see. Others have pointed out that it can also serve as a record of my personal progress and a collection of all the topics I delve into and try to understand, which is great.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>